http://www.undercoverquilts.com/terms-and-conditions.html

UNDERCOVER QUILTS AND FABRICS, SINCE 1990 FREE USA SHIPPING FOR ORDERS OVER $35.00 !!
Terms and Conditions
Use of our WebsiteDISCLAIMERThis Web Site and all Content available on this Web Site are provided without warranties of any kind. Undercover Quilts from the USA LLC, shall not be liable for any damages of any kind related to your use of this Web Site.INACCURACY DISCLAIMERFrom time to time, there may be information on our Web Site that contains typographical errors, inaccuracies, or omissions that may relate to product descriptions, pricing, and availability. Undercover Quilts from the USA LLC, reserves the right to correct any error, inaccuracies or omission and change or update information at any time without prior notice.
PRIVACY POLICYUndercover Quilts from the USA, LLC, is committed to protecting your privacy and any information you may share with us.What information do we collect?We collect information from you when you register on our site, place an order, subscribe to our mailing list, or fill out a form.When ordering or registering on our site, as appropriate, you may be asked to enter your: name, e-mail address, mailing address, phone number or credit card information. We will collect personal information only when it is voluntarily submitted.How do we use your information?Any of the information we collect from you may be used in one of the following ways:To personalize your experience (your information helps us to better respond to your individual needs).To improve our website (we continually strive to improve our website offerings based on the information and feedback we receive from you).To improve customer service (your information helps us to more effectively respond to your customer service requests and support needs).To process transactions (your information, whether public or private, will not be sold, exchanged, transferred, or given to any other company for any reason whatsoever, without your consent, other than for the express purpose of delivering the purchased product or service requested).To administer a contest, promotion, survey or other site feature.To send periodic emails (the email address you provide for order processing, may be used to send you information and updates pertaining to your order.Please note: If at any time you would like to unsubscribe from receiving future emails, we include detailed unsubscribe instructions at the bottom of each email.How do we protect visitor information?We implement a variety of security measures to maintain the safety of your personal information when you place an order or enter, submit, or access your personal information.We offer the use of a secure server. All supplied sensitive credit information is transmitted via Secure Socket Layer (SSL) technology and then encrypted into our payment gateway providers’ database only to be accessible by those authorized with special access rights to such systems, and are required to keep the information confidential.After a transaction, your private information, (credit cards, financial information, etc.) will not be stored in our servers.Do we use “cookies”?Yes. (Cookies are small files that a site or its service provider transfers to your computer’s hard drive through you Web browsers (if you allow) that enables the sites or service providers systems to recognize your browsers and capture and remember certain information. We use cookies to help us remember and process the items in your shopping cart and understand and save your preferences for future visits. If you prefer, you can choose to have your computer warn you each time a cookie is being sent, or you can choose to turn off all cookies via your browser settings. Like most websites, if your turn your cookies off, some of our services may not function properly. However, you can still place orders by contacting us directly during normal business hours by calling 800-469-6511 or 206 622 6382.Do we disclose any information to outside parties?We do not sell, trade, or otherwise transfer to outside parties your personally identifiable information. This does not include trusted third parties who assist us in operating our website, conducting our business, or servicing you, so long as those parties agree to keep this information confidential. We may also release your information when we believe release is appropriate to comply with the law, enforce our site policies, or protect ours or others rights, property or safety. However, non-personally identifiable visitor information may be provided to other parties for marketing, advertising, or other uses.Third party linksOccasionally, at our discretion, we may include or offer third party products or services on our website. These third party services have separate and independent privacy policies. We therefore have no responsibility or liability for the content and activities of these linked sites. Nonetheless, we seek to protect the integrity of our site and welcome any feedback.Changes to this privacy policyOur privacy policy may be updated at any time. When we update our policy, we will revise the update at the bottom of this page. You acknowledge and agree that it is your responsibility to review this privacy policy periodically and become aware of any modifications.Our privacy policy was last updated on March 1, 2019
Store
About
Contact
Artists
Blog
Media
Terms and Conditions
New Page
You:
::content::
::agent_name::
::content::
::content::
::content::
